

# ALISA GORDIEVSKAYA

+420 774 128 711 gordievskaya.alisa@gmail.com Prague, Czech Republic

#### BIO

After 3 years working both as a team member and manager, I decided to take a break for study and moved to Prague for newchallenges. I am the most engaged when I can help others to work together effectively, be it a school or work project or even in my daily life. Now I am looking for opportunities and strongly believe that when you do what you like you can translate passion into results.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## • HEAD OF NEW HOMES SALES

Etagi Real Estate | Jun 2015 - Feb 2016 | Chelyabinsk Leading team of 3 people, supporting operation of agents` sales department.

Main responsibilities:

Sales process coordination, from a prospect to a signed deal. Sales team recruitment and training.

Regular sales department indicators analysis.

Data summaries and reporting for senior management.

Marketing communication planning, vendor selection, trade events coordination.

Real estates selection, negotiation with developers.

## INFORMATION SUPPORT TEAM LEAD

Etagi Real Estate | Aug 2014 - Jun 2015 | Chelyabinsk

Leading team of 3 people.

Main responsibilities:

Marketing communication planning, vendor selection.

Coordinating CRM system usage, including new user training and content management.

Analysis of customer service quality.

 $Responsible \ for \ the \ department's \ development \ strategy.$ 

#### • OFFICE MANAGER

Etagi Real Estate | Apr 2014 - Jul 2014 | Chelyabinsk Main responsibilities:

Maintaining administrative duties to ensure smooth

operation of the real estate agency office.

Customer support, quality assurance.

CRM system user support.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### MSc MANAGEMENT

High School of Economics (VŠE) | Sep 2016 - Jul 2019 | Prague

Minor Degree: Project Management

Agile Project Management course absolvent.

#### STUDENT PROJECT CONTEST - MAIN AWARD

High School of Economics (VŠE) | Dec 2016 | Prague

Project Management course.

Client - Česká spořitelna.

Developing a marketing strategy for attracting younger customers.

### Bc. (HONS) CRISIS MANAGEMENT

South-Ural State University | Sep 2008 - May 2013 | Chelyabinsk

 $\label{eq:main_study} \textit{Main study areas: Economics, Management}$ 

Thesis: Concentrated Growth Strategy

## LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY





### SKILLS

Agile Project Management Framework

M S Office

MS Project

Google Adwords

Trello

JIRA

Gretl

Bitrix 24